



apeksha.fortune@gmail.com



7838047826



Gurgaon

#### **SKILLS**

Manual Testing

Mobile Application Testing

Android & iOS Mobile App Testing

API Testing (Postman)

Bug Tracker:-Jira, Gitlab

Browserstack

Test Plan

Test execution

Test Cases Preparation in Xray/Zephyre

Agile/Scrum

**Functional Testing** 

Smoke Testing

Regression Testing

Odoo ERP

Android Studio

### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hind

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

# Apeksha Gaur

Senior Test Consultant

Trustworthy Senior QA Engineer with 5.8 years of practical experience and a dedicated work ethic. Self-motivated to consistently provide first-class results in line with stringent targets and deadlines. Energetic self-starter and team builder. Navigate high-stress situations and achieve goals on time and under budget. Works with clients to determine requirements and provide excellent service

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Test Consultant Lead Capgemini Technology Services India Limited

04/2022 - Present

Roles and Responsibilities -

- Working as a Senior test consultant in Mobile application testing, Manual QA lead engineer
- Working in Agile Methodology & Leading a team of 5 members here, along with Manager
- Collaborate with QA Engineers to develop effective strategies and test plans
- Execute test cases and analyze results
- Evaluate story tickets according to Acceptance Criteria
- Report bugs and errors to development teams through Jira Xray/Zephyre
- Help troubleshoot issues, Check API's failed Response
- Provide sign off on applications ready to enter the UAT and PROD stage
- Work with cross-functional teams to ensure quality throughout the software development lifecycle
- Responsible for Daily and Weekly Status reports.

# **Software Test Engineer**Webkul Software Pvt Ltd

08/2018 - 03/2022

3/2022 Noida

Roles and Responsibilities -

- Worked on Odoo Mobikul Demo Live Apps and client customizations.
- Was responsible for all Website/Odoo backend/Applications for Android/iOS such as Odoo Marketplace, Odoo POS Apps, and Odoo Delivery Boy App.
- Understanding the requirement and Test Plan- with Manager & Developers
- Involved in Writing Test Cases & Test Scenarios & Reviewing Test Cases
- Involved in Application Testing- Functionality, Crashes, Deep testing, Odoo Core Testing, UI/UX, Regression, Smoke, Sanity Integration testing, Compatibility and End to end testing.
- For POS app testing used Android & iOS Tablets
- API Testing if all APIs are working fine for the Apps
- Reporting Issues on Gitlab

# **Test Analyst**Functionize Software Pvt Ltd

11/2017 - 06/2018

Noida

Guraaon

Roles and Responsibilities -

- Worked on Functionize Automation Tool, Manual Testing,
- Worked on Web App Testing for different US Based clients
- Projects worked on here were Agvance, TOTVS, Hearst, Marlabs
- Was responsible for creating Test cases and debugging and giving final Bug report to client



in

linkedin.com/in/apekshagaur-a6b32a8b

### **SOFT SKILLS**

Presentation Skills

Prioritization

**Conflict Resolution** 

Team Work

Team Management

Quality Assurance

Responsible

### **INTERESTS**

e-commerce domain

banking domain

Healthcare domain

Mobile App Testing

Android

iOS

Browserstack

Manual Testing

Jira

**API Testing** 

# Apeksha Gaur

Senior Test Consultant

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Software Test Consultant Capgemini

Achievements/Tasks

- Participated in all Scrum Meetings and give ideas helpful in improvement & enhancement of the Mobile Apps for better user experience
- Provided demo's, trainings and also groomed the team or new joiners to take them to next level
- Highlighting Blockers & critical bugs on early basis to deliver features on time

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Completed Software Testing course from Qspiders Noida in 2017

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Received client appreciation, and increased Playstore & Trustpilot positive reviews for many client customizations and demo Apps

Won Attendence Hero Award in Webkul

#### **PROJECTS**

Title: Tested all Odoo Mobikul Live Apps on playstore & Modules from Odoo Apps Store (08/2018 - 03/2022)

- Mobikul:Mobile App Builder: https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/13.0/mobikul/
- Odoo Marketplace Mobikul App: https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/13.0/mobikul\_multi\_vendor/
- □ Mobikul POS: Mobile Native App Builder: <a href="https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/mobikul\_pos/">https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/mobikul\_pos/</a>
- □ Mobikul Merge Category: https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/13.0/mobikul\_cat\_merge/
- ODOO SAAS KIT | ALL IN ONE: https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/odoo\_saas\_kit/
- Odoo Multi Vendor Marketplace : <a href="https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/odoo\_marketplace/">https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/odoo\_marketplace/</a>
- Odoo Delivery Boy: https://apps.odoo.com/apps/modules/16.0/mobikul\_multi\_vendor/

E-commerce Mobile App Testing for Europe/France/UK and more than 15 other countries (04/2022 - Present)

Was responsible for all end to end testing of Mobile Apps as a QA Lead for a timely delivery to Go Live

### **EDUCATION**

# B.E. in Electronics & Communication Engineering.

Rajiv Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya

07/2008 - 06/2012 Ujjain M.P.

**High School**Girls School, Shivpuri M.P.

83%